We said that during this lecture, at least up to now, we've used a hybrid network because we use our own
gateway, but the network server doesn't belong to us.
Great.
But actually the TTN networks server provides a little bit more.
It also provides network coverage in addition to my own coverage.
It means that I can, of course, benefit from my gateway coverage, but I can also benefit from all
of the gateway registered on this network server.
This is called a community network.
The more user they are in the community, the more coverage there is for everyone.
And sometimes it's even free.
If we come back to the Alliance website, then we can select the area,
we're interested in.
And for example, in France, there is two community network available so far.
And if you register on this instance, then you will know the coverage you can expect.
So now that we know everything about network type, public private, hybrid community, then we'll see
that whatever type of network the user will need to use, a loved one network is always the same.
So in the next video, we'll try to provide a clear explanation on the network configuration.